point2agent.com 2003-12-08

# Point2 Agent - Powerful Website Software For Real Estate

**10 Principles**

Point2 is committed to maintaining the accuracy, confidentiality and security of personal information. We have accepted 10 Principles established by the Canadian Standards Association's Model Code. They are as follows: 

**Accountability**  
Point2 employees are responsible for maintaining and protecting personal information under their control. Point2has designated an individual to oversee the company's compliance with the 10 principles. 

**Identifying Purposes**  
We identify the purposes for which personal information is collected.

**Consent**  
We only collect, use and disclose your personal information with your knowledge and consent, except where otherwise required or permitted by law.

**Limiting Collection**  
We limit collection of your personal information to only those details that are necessary for the purposes identified.

**Limiting Use, Disclosure and Retention**  
Personal information is only used or disclosed for the purpose that it was collected, unless otherwise consented, or when required or permitted by law. We only retain your personal information for the period of time required to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected.

**Accuracy**  
We keep personal information we collect as accurate, complete and up-to-date as necessary to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected.

**Safeguards**  
We protect personal information we collect with security safeguards appropriate to the sensitivity of the information.

**Openness**  
Information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information is made readily available to you.

**Access**  
At your request, we inform you of the existence, use and disclosure of your personal information, and provide access to the information. You can challenge the accuracy and completeness of your information, and amend it as necessary.

**Challenging Compliance**  
You can contact us with any questions, complaints or suggestions with respect to the above principles.
